Every single day there's something new you can plan for
每天都有新鲜东西把你等待
Every single day there's something wonderful to do
每天无论做些什么都能很精彩
But nothing makes me happy like a day that I can say
可有件开心事情 我不禁要说出来
"Today I planned a party, and it's just for you!"
“今天我办的派对只为你而开”
How's it going today, Pinkie?
今天怎么样 萍琪？
Great, thanks! Got any streamers today?
很棒 谢啦 今天有彩带卖吗？
You betcha! Big party planned?
当然有 要开大派对吗？
Don't you know it!
那还用说嘛
Don't have much time to gather all the things I need
准备的事项太多 时间过太快
If I'm really gonna make this party fly
可是我要让这聚会办出彩
For today's another day that all of Ponyville will say
因为今天小马镇一定交口来称赞
There goes the super party pony Pinkie Pie!
快看那超级派对明星萍琪派
She planned our first foal shower
where we played all sorts of games
她为宝宝的淋浴带来各种小游戏
Having so much fun as we chose Pound and Pumpkin's names
欢笑声中为他们俩开心把名起
She planned my cute-ceañera my dad made me, I won't lie
我的可爱大联欢爸爸让她为我办
I demanded all the best, I suppose she passed the test
我想要的是最好 她过了我这一关
Sure it was pretty good all thanks to Pinkie Pie
联欢会还不错 多亏萍琪派
Thanks, I guess?
还是…谢谢啦
What color paints do you need?
您要什么样的颜色？
I'm gonna need the full rainbow!
我要整条彩虹的颜色
A paintbrush too?
还要画刷吗？
Yes, if you please!
也要 多谢啦
And what from me?
我能给什么？
Your biggest banner! This party's gonna be the best!
最大号的横幅 这派对一定要办到最棒
Haha I don't doubt it!
毫无疑问啦
Every single day there's something new we can plan for
每天都有新鲜东西把你等待
Every single day there's something wonderful to try
每天无论做些什么都能很精彩
But nothing makes us happy like a day that we can say
可有件开心事情 我们共同在期待
"Today there'll be a party planned by Pinkie Pie!"
因为今天的派对全靠萍琪开
I don't know how she does it.
不知道她怎么做到的
Wow, look at her go!
看她的动作
Oh, boy! This is gonna be good!
伙计 这下肯定差不了
Go, Pinkie, go!
加油 萍琪 加油
There's no other pony like her, no pony that could be
她就是独一无二 没有谁能匹敌
As great! As fun!
精彩! 好玩!
As our super party pony Pinkie!
就属派对明星小马萍琪